<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scene on 唐山晋水</title>
    <link>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/tags/scene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scene on 唐山晋水</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://firebirdsoul.github.io/tags/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/2017/04/chapter-vi-esmeralda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/2017/04/chapter-vi-esmeralda/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/2017/04/chapter-iv-master-jacques-coppenole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/2017/04/chapter-iv-master-jacques-coppenole/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/2017/04/chapter-i-the-grand-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://firebirdsoul.github.io/2017/04/chapter-i-the-grand-hall/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>